好吧  那我们在佛罗里达再开张
Okay. So we'll open in Florida?
不  孩子  不行  没办法
No, kid, can't. You can't.
水质不同  饼皮也不同
The water's not the same so the crust wouldn't be either.
我给你空运纽约的水
Well, I'll fly in the New York water.
有人专门做这个
People do it.
不了
Nah.
你知道  我该享受阳光沙滩了
You know, beach time for me.
平静  宁静的生活
Calm, calm.
这样  我给你垫付钱
Lefs do this. I'll advance you the money
这样你就能买下你看中的房产
so you can get that property that you want.
同时不卖掉你的餐厅
Against a purchase price.
然后你为这里培训一位接班人
Meanwhile, you train a replacement for here,
冬天去南边待上一两个月
spend a couple of months in the winter down there.
神清气爽地回来
Come back refreshed.
我们计划  大概五年后
And we plan for, what, five years from now,